Welcome.
欢迎。
Let's first create a C++ project for us to work with.
让我们首先创建一个C++项目，让我们使用。
And here I'm going to select the third person template as our starting point.
在这里我将选择第三人称模板作为我们的起点。
Since it contains all the boilerplate movement code that we need, it can really help us to
因为它包含了所有我们需要的模板运动代码，它可以真正帮助我们
save some time and focus on the actual implementation of our climbing system.
它可以帮助我们节省一些时间，把精力放在攀爬系统的实际实现上。
So after having the third person selected, this is where I want to put my project.
所以在选择了第三人称之后，我想把我的项目放在这里。
And I'm going to name my project Climbing System and make sure you select this C++.
我将把我的项目命名为 "攀登系统"，并确保你选择了这个C++。
Then I'm going to click create.
然后我将点击创建。
So after creating the project, this is what you should see inside of third person template.
所以在创建项目后，这就是你在第三人称模板中应该看到的东西。
Now if I click play, you can see I can already run around using the existing character.
现在，如果我点击播放，你可以看到我已经可以使用现有的角色到处跑了。
And if I go to my Visual Studio inside of the climbing system, go to source and inside
如果我进入Visual Studio的攀岩系统，进入源代码，在攀岩系统这个文件夹中
of this folder climbing system, these are all the files that we currently have.
这个文件夹中的攀岩系统，这些是我们目前拥有的所有文件。
So our character class is called ClimbingSystemCharacter.h.
所以我们的角色类被称为ClimbingSystemCharacter.h。
I'm going to open it.
我将打开它。
Like I said, all the boilerplate code has already been done for us.
就像我说的，所有的模板代码都已经为我们完成了。
So we have components for the camera, for the spring arm, and we also have a good starting
所以我们有摄像机和弹簧臂的组件，我们也有一个很好的默认增强输入系统的起点。
point for the default enhanced input system.
默认的增强型输入系统的起点。
We're going to look into this code later.
我们将在后面研究这些代码。
And one more thing that I like to mention is inside of this level prototyping filter,
还有一件事我想提及的是在这个水平原型过滤器里面、
inside of meshes, you can see you already have some basic primitive shapes that we can
在网格里面，你可以看到你已经有一些基本的原始形状，我们可以
use and later we can use them to build the surfaces that we can climb.
以后我们可以用它们来构建我们可以攀爬的表面。
And it's time for a challenge.
现在是进行挑战的时候了。
So a challenge is simple.
所以挑战很简单。
I'd like you to create a C++ project based on the third person template.
我想让你在第三人称模板的基础上创建一个C++项目。
This should be a fairly easy challenge.
这应该是一个相当容易的挑战。
Pause the video now and give this a go and I'll see you in the next lecture.
现在暂停视频，给它一个机会，我们在下一个讲座中见。
[Music]
[音乐]